{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Drafting Services","__cache./api/resource/task/40214/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40214,"taskName":"Draftsperson/CADD","taskDescription":"Draftsperson or CADD Expert (Non-Designer)","xmTaskDescriptor":"Drafting Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":57,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Architect Person hire engineer engineering","textMessagingName":"Cad Draft","rolloverLongDesc":"Helps formalize drawings \u0026 prepare blueprints for projects. Often uses CAD (Computer Aided Design) software. Might work with a designer, architect or homeowner.","rolloverShortDesc":"Prepare project drawings.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Draftsperson or CADD Expert (Non-Designer).  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Drafting Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | CAD, Architectural \u0026 Residential Drafting","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Draftsperson/CADD","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Draftsperson/CADD","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Draftsperson / CADD Need","urlName":"Draftsperson-CADD","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Drafting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor | CAD, Architectural Drafters","searchKeywords":"Architect,Person,hire,engineer,engineering,draftperson,architecture,architects,Draftsperson,Drafts,CADD,Drafter","emcCategoryOid":-12005,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":521,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40214/":{"taskOID":40214,"originalTaskOID":40214,"setID":521,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5015,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4158,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New custom home","answerDisplayText":"New custom home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home addition","answerDisplayText":"Home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home remodel","answerDisplayText":"Home remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4138,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New commercial building","answerDisplayText":"New commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","answerDisplayText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4052,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need drawings of existing building","answerDisplayText":"Need drawings of existing building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4159,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","answerDisplayText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5016,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1790,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cutouts/photos","answerDisplayText":"Cutouts/photos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5759,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Sketches","answerDisplayText":"Sketches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1067,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blueprints that need alteration","answerDisplayText":"Blueprints that need alteration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4974,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Purchased plans that need modification","answerDisplayText":"Purchased plans that need modification","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5017,"questionDisplayText":"Neighborhood covenants","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does the development have Covenants, Codes and Restrictions (CC\u0026R) that must be followed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5019,"questionDisplayText":"Other Issues","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do any of the following issues need to be considered? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7209,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Zoning variance needed","answerDisplayText":"Zoning variance needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Environmental concerns","answerDisplayText":"Environmental concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5015,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4158,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New custom home","answerDisplayText":"New custom home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home addition","answerDisplayText":"Home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home remodel","answerDisplayText":"Home remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4138,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New commercial building","answerDisplayText":"New commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","answerDisplayText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4052,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need drawings of existing building","answerDisplayText":"Need drawings of existing building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4159,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","answerDisplayText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4158,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New custom home","answerDisplayText":"New custom home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home addition","answerDisplayText":"Home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home remodel","answerDisplayText":"Home remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4138,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New commercial building","answerDisplayText":"New commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","answerDisplayText":"Tenant improvement to commercial building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4052,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need drawings of existing building","answerDisplayText":"Need drawings of existing building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4159,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","answerDisplayText":"New drawings converted to CADD software","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5016,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1790,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cutouts/photos","answerDisplayText":"Cutouts/photos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5759,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Sketches","answerDisplayText":"Sketches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1067,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blueprints that need alteration","answerDisplayText":"Blueprints that need alteration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4974,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Purchased plans that need modification","answerDisplayText":"Purchased plans that need modification","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1790,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cutouts/photos","answerDisplayText":"Cutouts/photos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5759,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Sketches","answerDisplayText":"Sketches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1067,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blueprints that need alteration","answerDisplayText":"Blueprints that need alteration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4974,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Purchased plans that need modification","answerDisplayText":"Purchased plans that need modification","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5017,"questionDisplayText":"Neighborhood covenants","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does the development have Covenants, Codes and Restrictions (CC\u0026R) that must be followed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5019,"questionDisplayText":"Other Issues","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do any of the following issues need to be considered? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7209,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Zoning variance needed","answerDisplayText":"Zoning variance needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Environmental concerns","answerDisplayText":"Environmental concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7209,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Zoning variance needed","answerDisplayText":"Zoning variance needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Environmental concerns","answerDisplayText":"Environmental concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}